Now, you see,
this is what we could be
doing on a holiday.
Not all the hiking-up-mountains stuff
you're planning.
Tickles. Tickles.
You want me to stop?
No.
But it's 6:15.
- 6:15?
- Mmm-hmm.
Oh, I gotta go.
I'll cook tonight.
Don't even think about it.
It's pouring.
- Freddie! Ooh, whoa!
- Watch it!
Yeah, listen, I'm on it.
All right, the West Coast
will still be up.
I'll call Carmichael now
and we can close this.
Taxi!
Yeah, we won't. Don't worry.
Look out!
Bye now!
Take care, John!
Um... How many in this one?
170 calories.
You did have that one yesterday.
What about that one, then?
220.
But it is less
if you eat them standing up.
- Oh!
- Yeah. Should we put them in a bag?
- Please. Come on.
- Yeah! Thanks, Frank.
I don't think I can finish this.
Shall we wrap it up for you, Daphne?
Have it later? Yeah.
I'm really sorry.
A month's money.
That's big of him.
Given she's worked
like a Trojan in that cafe
for the past six years.
He's closing down, love. He had no choice.
What the hell is she gonna do now?
Treena can't get any more
hours in the flower shop.
Lou will get another job.
She has a lot of potential.
There are no jobs, Josie. I should know.
Look, I'm just saying,
we needed that money.
Let's not panic, eh?
She'll find something. Won't you, Lou?
That's it, Callum! Go on!
Run With me, babe!
- Come on!
- Nah. Uh-uh.
- Only got two laps to go.
- Oh, God!
You just gotta get back out there.
Think what you wanna do.
- Estate agent, maybe.
- Ooh! Yeah.
Shop assistant. Catering.
Do we have to discuss this again?
Well, you can't just mope around.
All the best entrepreneurs,
they fight their way back
from rock-bottom.
Just look at me, eh!
Oh! But I'm not you, Pat.
I toast tea cakes.
Look, can't you slow down?
I'm wearing the wrong bra.
I'm just saying,
put on a smile, and head back
to the job center.
Don't worry about the holiday.
I'll pay-
So the last two weeks,
we've tried the chicken
processing factory...
I'm still having nightmares
about those giblets.
- We've tried beautician.
- Turns out
hot wax is not my friend.
I'm running out of options
for you here, Louisa.
Syed, please! I'll take anything.
Oh!
This is new in.
It's not far from your home.
But you might need to do something
about your wardrobe for this one.
Hmm?
Care and companionship for a disabled man.
What kind Of care?
Needs someone to drive, feed and assist.
Six-month, fixed-term contract.
Oh! And it's good money.
It's actually excellent money.
It's the fifth time
they've tried to recruit.
They're desperate.
There's nothing on here
about needing skills.
It's perfect for you.
Yeah?
I know it's not how you like to dress.
Is it how anyone likes to dress?
- It served me very well.
- Oh!
In 1983!
Styles change, love,
- but smart remains smart.
- Uh-huh.
- Thank you.
- Bye, love.
Oh!
- You must be Louisa Clark.
- Yeah.
I'm Camilla Traynor. Do come in.
Please, sit down.
Oh, okay.
Do you have any experience of caregiving?
Um, I've never done it,
but I'm sure I could learn.
Do you have any experience
with quadriplegia?
Er, no.
We are talking about complete
loss of the legs,
and very limited use
of the arms and the hands.
Would that bother you?
Not as much as it would
bother him. Obviously.
Sorry.
Sorry. No, I didn't... No, uh...
No, I...
- Are you all right?
- Um, I'm...
I'm just a little hot.
Do you mind if I take off my jacket?
Your previous employer, here, says
you are a warm, chatty
and life-enhancing presence
with a lot of potential.
Yes, I paid him.
So, what exactly do you
want to do with your life?
Sorry?
Do you have aspirations for a career,
or a professional dream
that you wish to pursue?
- Um, well...
- Miss Clark,
why should I employ you
instead of, say, the previous candidate?
Um...
Really, you can't think of a single reason
why I should employ you?
Well, no. Yes, Mrs. Traynor.
I'm...
I'm a fast learner.
And I'm never ill.
And I only live on
the other side of the castle.
And I'm stronger than I look.
And I just...
I make a mean cup of tea.
You know, there really isn't
much that can't be solved
by a decent cup of tea.
Not that I'm saying that your husband's
paraplegia... Quadriplegia
- can be solved by...
- My husband?
It's my son.
Your son.
Will was injured in
a road accident two years ago.
Oh, I'm sorry.
When I'm nervous, I just say stupid stuff.
I'm just popping out.
Oh, another interviewee.
Will you be back this evening?
I'll do my best. Why?
Do you need me for something?
No, darling. Fine.
Hello. I'm Stephen. Will's father.
Louisa Clark.
Nice to meet you.
Lovely to meet you.
- See you later, darling.
- Mmm-hmm.
So.
Hmm.
Would you like the job?
Yes!
Can you start immediately?
Good.
Then let's go and meet Will.
Right, yeah. Okay. Um, sure.
The hours are 8:00 to 5:00,
Monday to Saturday.
If, for whatever reason,
you're running late
or you need to leave early,
- please call and let me know.
- Okay.
I must stress
that Will should not be left alone
for longer than 15 minutes.
And, uh...
You might want to wear something
a little less revealing.
Oh, yes, of course.
This is the annex.
It was the stables before
we had it adapted for Will.
Um, I'll give you a set of car keys,
and put you on the insurance.
Nathan will show you how to use the ramp.
There's a bathroom in here.
Tea and coffee are in this cupboard here.
You're welcome to help yourself.
And there is always food in the fridge.
You and Will can work out
your level of interaction yourselves.
Um, obviously...
Well, I would hope that you could get on.
It would be nice if he could
think of you as a friend
rather than a paid professional.
Do you have any questions?
No.
Then let's introduce you to Will.
He should be dressed by now.
He has good days and bad days.
Mrs. Traynor, I won't let you down.
Good.
I have someone to meet you.
Yeah, he's decent, Mrs. T.
Will, this is Louisa Clark.
I'm Lou!
Will.
William.
William, please.
Hello, Louisa Clark. I'm Will Traynor.
You appear to have a problem
with your skirt.
You're a bad man, Mr. T.
G'day. I'm Nathan.
Right.
Well, I'll leave you to get on.
Miss Clark, Nathan will talk you
through Will's routines and equipment.
You don't have to talk across me, Mother.
My brain isn't paralyzed.
Yet.
I'm Lou!
Yeah. You already said that.
Shall I make us all a cup of tea?
Wrench! Where's my wrench?
Mum, did you turn down the gas on my veg?
That's the cutlery drawer, Bernard.
And you're getting oil everywhere.
Everything will be soggy again.
Yeah, well, things turn up in
strange places in this house.
- Auntie Lou! Auntie Lou!
- Oh!
- You got it, didn't you?
- Uh...
Yeah!
Yay!
Louisa Clark, working for the Traynors.
Wonders will never cease.
Uh, yeah.
Okay.
This tells you pretty much
everything you need to know.
Now, I do most of the heavy lifting,
but there's a timetable here
so you can see what he has, when.
I have to handle drugs?
Blood-pressure meds to raise it
in the morning when he gets up.
Anti-spasm tablets.
Four times a day
to control muscular spasms.
Tablets for nerve pain.
Um, now, you can give him
painkillers, if he asks.
Just try to resist giving him
sleeping pills, if possible.
They tend to make him
a little bit, um, you know, irritable.
No, uh... More irritable.
It's a lot to remember.
Well, it's all written down.
You know, he knows what's what.
Though, he might deny it.
And you got my number.
Most of my other patients are nearby,
so I'm never far away.
What if he needs to... Uh...
No, don't worry.
You're not here for
any of the physical stuff.
What am I here for?
To cheer him up, I guess.
Hello.
So I thought we could
go out this afternoon.
Where do you have in mind?
Well, I was told that you had a car
that was adapted for wheelchair use.
And you thought a drive
would be good for me.
A breath of fresh air.
What do you usually do?
I don't do anything, Miss Clark.
I sit. I just about exist.
Okay. Well, I could get you your computer.
Have you found a good quad
support group I could join?
Quads "R" Us?
The Tin Wheels Club?
Or perhaps we could
get to know each other a bit.
You know, because then you could tell me
what you do like to do.
May...
Maybe.
Here's what I know about you, Miss Clark.
My mother says you're chatty.
Yeah.
Can we strike a deal?
Whereby you are very un-chatty around me?
Okay.
Yeah, well, I'll just be in the kitchen
if, you know, need anything.
Lovely.
So, how was he?
He done his Stephen Hawking impression yet
or just stuck with My Left Foot?
Ah, he's fine!
Okay. Well, you can take lunch now.
Me and Mr. T. have a few things
to take care of at this time of day.
Good morning!
Hi!
Not a great day.
Would you like a cup of tea?
Sorry.
Val d'lsere.
Good snow that year.
Sorry. I was... I was...
You were just looking at my photographs,
thinking how awful it must be
to have lived like that
and ended up like this.
The rest are in the drawer
if you'd like to snoop around further.
Good morning.
Every time I speak,
he looks at me like I'm stupid.
To be fair, you are pretty stupid.
Yeah, but he doesn't know that yet.
Maybe he's like that with everyone
until he knows whether
they're gonna stick around.
I mean, it's only been 10 days.
Feels like a lifetime.
Well, you can't quit, Lou.
Yeah? Watch me.
Um...
Look, I'm thinking of
going back to college.
Someone's dropped out of business studies
and they can take me back.
What? What about Thomas?
There's a nursery on campus.
We'd come back at weekends.
I don't have a Patrick, Lou.
I don't think I'm ever gonna
have a Patrick.
I need this.
Oh, I get it.
You just need me to stay here
in my miserable job,
so I can help Mum and Dad.
- I've done my fair share.
- Yeah?
I can't stay here.
You know I can't.
Please, for me and Tom.
Louisa, some visitors are on their way.
Friends of Will's. It's unexpected.
You might need to...
Oh, I'll make some tea or coffee.
And I'll make myself scarce.
Yes, that would be good.
I think I'll...
I think I'll leave them to it.
So how's the physio and stuff?
All coming on? Any improvements?
No.
Well, you look great.
- Yeah.
- So...
So.
To what do I owe this pleasure?
I'm sorry it's been so long.
I've been so busy.
They've been really working me hard.
I mean, weekends.
Yeah, things are manic at the office, too.
New chap from New York.
Bains! You ever come across him at all?
No.
Fearsome. Total monster!
Most days I feel I can
hardly leave my chair.
Please say something.
Congratulations.
Neither of us meant for this to happen.
We were just friends for ages.
And if truth be told,
Rupert was the most terrific
support after your accident.
Big of him.
Oh, Will, please. l...
We should probably go.
I'm sorry, Will. I really am.
We both are.
And I... We really do hope
things improve for you.
Thank you.
You know, I tried for months.
He just pushed me away.
Didn't want me here.
You can only help someone
who actually wants to be helped.
I was wondering if you wanted me to...
Right, well, you better not move
until I've cleaned that up because
I've got no idea what I'd do
if you pop a tire.
It was awful!
It's his girlfriend and his best friend.
You can't blame her.
Are you really saying that
you'd stick around with me
if I was paralyzed from the neck down?
Of course I would.
Well, I wouldn't want someone
staying with me out of pity.
I mean, strangers wipe your arse. Jesus!
And think of all the things
you couldn't do.
No more running, no more cycling.
No more sex.
Of course, you could have sex.
It's just the girl would
have to be on top.
- Oh, well, we'd be doomed, then.
- Mmm.
- Hey, listen.
- Yeah.
- About the holiday.
How do you fancy...
Norway?
Norway.
Wow.
Yeah! Okay. Whoo!
- Great!
- Yeah.
Boys, I'm in.
- What?
- Yes! Nice one!
Um, no, wait.
We're, you're in what?
The Viking Triathlon.
Sixty miles on a bike, 30 miles on foot,
and then a nice swim
through sub-zero Nordic seas.
Yeah!
That's our holiday?
Yeah, but not all of it.
Just the beginning,
and then we'll sightsee, or whatever.
Look, I have never been fitter, Lou.
This is the year to do it.
I just thought I'd see
if I could fix some of these.
Or, um, if you wanted to get new ones,
I could go into town at lunch time.
Or we could both go.
Do you know what, Louisa?
Me smashing those photographs
was not an accident.
Sorry. I didn't think...
You thought you knew best.
Well, I don't want those
pictures staring at me
every time I'm stuck in bed,
waiting for someone to bloody
get me out again. Okay?
I wasn't going to fix the one of Alicia.
I'm not that stupid.
Spare me the cod psychology.
Just go and raid your grandma's wardrobe,
or whatever it is you do
when you're not making tea.
You don't have to be an arse!
Your friends got the shitty treatment.
Fine. They deserved it.
I'm just trying to do my job
as best I can.
So it would be really nice
if you didn't try and make
my life as miserable
as you apparently make everyone else's.
What if I said I didn't want you here?
I'm not employed by you.
I'm employed by your mother.
So unless she says she doesn't want me
here anymore, I'm staying.
Not because I care about you,
or particularly enjoy your company,
but because I need the money.
I really need the money.
Just put them in the drawer.
Hi. Am I needed?
DVD weather, I think.
Des Hommes Et Des Dieux.
Something about men?
Yes, it's French gay porn.
You really don't enjoy sarcasm, do you?
Sarcasm is fine.
I just don't like superiority.
You must hate me, then.
I've never hated anyone.
Let me know if you need anything.
Have you seen it?
I don't really like those kind of films.
Those kind of films?
Films with subtitles.
What, did your school
not teach you to read?
Sh' down.
Watch this with me. That's an order.
- So?
- Well, they could have left.
- They chose to stay.
- Yeah, no, I get it.
Being there gave their lives more meaning.
- But that's...
- But you don't agree.
Well, to sacrifice themselves like that!
I mean, could you even imagine?
But you liked the film?
I loved it
Oh, if you're laughing at me,
I swear to God,
I'll push you out that chair.
I'm not laughing at you.
The sky is clearing.
Shall we get some air?
I'm just amazed
that you could reach
the ripe old age of, what?
Twenty-six.
Twenty-six, and never have
watched a film with subtitles.
Oh, well, I'm just amazed
that you've reached the ripe old age of 31
without being locked in a cupboard
for being such a snob.
What?
E. T. is my favorite film.
E. T. is everyone's favorite film.
- I've seen every Bond.
- So has the world.
And I've got a soft spot for Armageddon.
Bruce Willis.
Oil driller has to save the world
from an asteroid. He does.
That's better.
So what do you do with yourself
when you're not here, Louisa Clark?
I, uh... I spend time with my family.
And I go to the pub.
I watch TV.
I... Oh, I watch Patrick running.
- Patrick's your boyfriend?
- Yeah.
But you don't run with him?
I'm not exactly built for it.
This is an impressive list of hobbies.
Well, no, no. Okay, I read a bit.
And I like clothes.
You like clothes?
I don't do much, okay?
I go to work and I go home, and that's it.
Wow.
Your life's even duller than mine.
He's in a good mood.
He told me all about you offering him
the pasta with green gravy.
I've... I've never
had pesto sauce before.
No, whatever. It's all good.
It's a long time since
he's laughed at anything.
Hey.
Hello there, Mr. Traynor.
How are you doing today?
Nathan, what are they doing in there?
He has a checkup every six months.
To see if he's getting better?
No, it's a spinal-cord injury.
He's not... He's not going to get better.
But you do all those exercises with him.
Yeah. That's to stop
his muscles atrophying.
Will's body no longer works below here.
Yeah, but he's still trying, right?
He threw everything
into physio the first year,
and all he got from it was
slight movement in his thumb and finger.
Then the first bout of pneumonia hit,
then autonomic dysreflexia...
What does that mean?
Right. So his blood pressure
- goes up and down.
- Yeah.
He's constantly open to infection.
But there's medical advances
taking place all the time. Right?
Well, yeah.
But no one's worked out
how to fix a spinal cord yet.
Oh, I hear this one's good.
Oh, because we suddenly speak Spanish?
No, it's got subtitles.
It gets so you don't notice after a while.
Two for the Will Ferrell, please.
Oh.
Is he okay?
He's not great. Bit of a chill.
Where's Nathan?
I've called him. He'll be here soon.
Look, Camilla's had to go up to London.
Are you going to be all right?
- Of course.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
I'm on my mobile, if you need me.
Okay.
Will, can I do anything?
My pillows aren't right.
Um, what do I do?
Put your hand under my head,
on my neck, and just lift gently.
Okay.
- Oh, Jesus.
- What have I done?
Your hands are freezing.
Better.
Can I get you some painkillers?
- Yeah? Okay.
- Thank you.
Will.
Will?
Will? It's...
It's Lou.
I know.
Is there something
I should be doing?
Some drugs or something?
I'm just getting really worried.
Hello. This is Stephen.
Please leave your name and number,
and I'll call you back.
Hi, Mr. Traynor. It's Lou. I'm just...
I'm getting concerned about Will
and I was wondering if
you could just call me back.
Okay. Thanks. Bye.
G'day. This is Nathan.
Leave a message and I'll call you back.
Don't ring Mum.
What?
We'll be fine, Clark.
Oi!
Sorry. Had to walk here.
Took ages, the bloody weather, you know.
How's things?
Not great. He's in and out
and he's not drunk anything.
How long's he been like this?
Maybe four or five hours.
I tried to call.
I did give him painkillers.
Might as well have given him M&Ms.
Well, he said he just wanted to sleep.
Yeah, it's in the folder, Lou.
Will doesn't sweat the way we do.
If he gets even a slight chill,
his temperature goes haywire.
- Yeah, but he said...
- Just go and get us a fan
- and a damp towel, real quick.
- Okay.
Hey, buddy. You all right?
Will? You all right?
I got you, mate. Come on.
Come on. Yeah.
Here.
Hey, focus. Lou, you gotta
watch what I'm doing.
- Sorry.
- That's right.
He's going to be okay.
There are very few people out there
who can claim to have
out-Bonded James Bond.
But birthday boy "Wild Willy" Will Traynor
is certainly one of them.
So, Will, any final thoughts, bro?
I'm thinking you should be next, mate.
Yeah, right!
We're all thinking it.
Is there really nothing he can't do?
- Do we hate him? Yes.
- We do!
But there's no point
in dwelling on that on his birthday.
Thank God he's not good-looking.
Ah, stop!
You're watching
French gay porn, I hope.
Wi-Fi connection's not strong enough.
What time is it?
Where's... Where's Nathan?
Half eight. He had to
go to another patient.
Snow got pretty bad.
Shouldn't you be at home?
You're stuck with me.
Will, can I ask you something?
I suspect you're going to.
What happened?
My mother didn't tell you?
It's her favorite story.
Some sort of traffic accident...
- Motorbike.
- You were riding a motorbike?
Actually, I wasn't.
The bike hit me.
Sorry. Sorry, I'm being chatty again,
and you need to rest.
No.
Sta)'-
Tell me...
Tell me something good.
I used to say that to my dad.
But if I told you what he said back,
you'd think I was insane.
Oh, that ship has sailed, Clark.
When I had a nightmare or
something he used to sing.
Go on.
He used to sing the Molahonkey song.
- The what?
- The Molahonkey song.
I thought everyone knew it.
Trust me, Clark. I'm a Molahonkey virgin.
You're gonna make me sing it now?
You're insane.
Your whole family is insane.
And you're a God-awful singer.
I hope your dad was better.
I think what you mean to say is,
"Thank you, Miss Clark,
for attempting to entertain me."
Okay, Clark.
Tell me something else.
Something that doesn't involve singing.
About what?
Anything-.
Well...
When I was little,
my mum got me a pair of glittery wellies,
and I refused to take them off.
I wore them in bed, in the bath,
all summer long.
My favorite outfit
was the glittery boots
and my bumblebee tights.
Bumblebee tights?
- Black and yellow stripes.
- Oh, dear God.
I just... I really, really, really
liked having stripy legs.
So what happened to these gorgeous wellies
and stripy tights?
Ah! I outgrew them.
It broke my heart.
And they don't make those tights anymore.
Not for grown women, anyway.
Strange, that.
Oh, you can mock. Didn't you
ever love anything that much?
Yes.
Yes, I did.
Interesting choice of footwear.
Patrick says they make me look
like a leprechaun drag queen.
He was being nice.
- Don't smile at me like that.
- Why not?
Because I don't know what it means.
Where did you pick up your exotic tastes?
- What do you mean by that?
- It can't be from around here.
Why not?
Because this is the kind of
place people come to
when they've got tired of actually living.
People here think excitement is a new
"Please be quiet" sign
going up in the library.
You should be out there,
claiming the world as your own.
Showing your leprechaun shoes
to dodgy men.
- I like my life.
- You like everything.
- I'm happy here.
- Well, you shouldn't be.
Oh, you want me to be more
like the girls you know, do you?
Go to London, marry somebody like Rupert.
I believe he's taken.
And ignore the fact that
he's shagging his secretary
within five years.
And bitch about him at dinner parties,
knowing he won't leave because
he's scared of the alimony.
And have sex once every six weeks,
and listen to him going on and on about
how much he adores the children,
while doing nothing
to actually take care of them.
And have perfect hair,
but get this kind of pinched face
through never saying
what you actually mean.
And develop an insane Pilates habit,
and buy a dog, or a horse,
and develop a crush
on your riding instructor.
And watch your husband take up
jogging when he hits 40
and buy a Harley.
And know that every day,
he goes into the office
and looks at the young men,
and feels like, somehow, he got suckered!
And leave him anyway, and come back here
to give the children a happy childhood.
Whoa!
There were a lot of divorce
handovers at the cafe.
Sorry.
How did you end up in that café?
Treena made a bet
that I couldn't get a job in 24 hours.
I proved her wrong.
And stayed there six years. Way to go!
I was supposed to leave.
I had a place at Manchester.
What were you going to study?
Fashion.
Mmm. So, why didn't you go?
You know what I see when I look at you?
- Don't say "potential."
- Potential.
You need to widen your horizons, Clark.
You only get one life.
It's actually your duty
to live it as fully as possible.
Well, you need a shave!
If that beard gets any longer,
I'll be picking food out of it.
And then I'll have to sue you
for undue distress in the workplace.
- You're changing the subject.
- Yes.
I am.
Fine.
I'll let you.
You're really going to do this?
I'm, uh...
I'm really gonna do this.
My mother's gonna be so happy.
Yes, well,
we won't let that put us off.
You've got a funny look on your face.
Please don't tell me
you shaved off my eyebrows.
Only the one.
Freedom? You call this freedom?
We all agreed to it.
Not the specifics. Jesus!
If I hadn't noticed the Swiss postmark...
We made an agreement with Will.
Six months.
No. I only agreed
so that we had six months
to change his mind.
I cannot believe that you are willing
to help our son end his life!
I'd rather that than
risk him trying again, alone.
It wasn't a cry for help, Camilla.
He meant it. You know that.
Now, this way we can be with him,
supporting him, loving him.
- He's my son!
- Yes, he's my son, too!
It's his choice. This is what he wants.
You know how much pain he's in.
He gave me six months.
We can still persuade him.
And you think the pretty waitress
is going to do that.
Now, can I have the letter, please?
Please.
Apparently, the shave was your idea.
Nice one! It looks great.
Now,
Arsenal, four. Liverpool, one.
Bye.
I need you.
I know we need the money,
but this is horrible.
I'm basically just on suicide watch.
I am not going back.
- Yeah.
- What?
Come on. Say it.
I was thinking about him.
Lou, you can't leave him.
They've got money, right?
I don't want their money!
No, not for you, idiot-girl!
Look.
If this is what he really wants,
then use the time he's got left.
Make it special.
Ask the Traynors for a budget
and go crazy.
Organize, I don't know,
swimming with dolphins, sky-diving.
A nice, sexy lap dance.
City boys always like a lap dance.
Katrina Clark!
A bucket list.
Show him how good this time can be.
Take him places. Make him laugh.
Bloody hell.
But, Treen, what if that list
could do more than that?
What if it could make him change his mind?
Will's barely left
the house in two years.
We have tried.
Yes, but we haven't succeeded.
If Louisa can come up with things
that Will is able and prepared to do,
then that's all for the good, surely.
Sports, concerts.
I'd love to see him
do any of these things.
Okay. Okay.
Louisa, if you can get me a schedule,
I'll see if I can shift things
around in my diary.
No!
Let him do it for himself.
Will needs to be allowed
to feel like a man.
There you go.
Oh, my God!
What have you come as?
I don't care what you think.
Even if you have got a new haircut.
You look like a madwoman.
An oddly cheerful madwoman.
We're taking Nathan
to see the horse racing.
Horse racing?
Yeah. Nathan's never been.
Yeah. It's true.
And, besides, I've got
five pounds on Man-Oh-Man
at eight to one.
My dad's mate, Jimmy,
says he's a sure thing.
Just a wild guess,
but you haven't been
racing before, either,
have you, Clark?
The perfect spot.
Look, we're so lucky.
Are you sure? This is too soft,
he's going to sink.
Oh, no. He'll be fine.
It's gonna be great.
Right. That's all right.
Yeah?
- Ah... Um...
- You all right?
- What, do we need to?
- Look, you pull and I'll push.
Okay.
Oh! Shit. Um...
Don't worry. It's only cashmere.
Yeah. He's stuck
I know, it's going to be fine.
It's gonna be fine.
- Oh, excuse me! Hi!
- You okay?
- Hi. Sorry. Do you...
- Clark.
Would you be able to help us?
With the, um...
- Because we're a bit stuck.
- We're fine.
- We're fine. We're fine.
- No, we're fine.
Yeah? Would that be... Very kind.
Come on, Will.
You okay? Yeah! You're okay, aren't you?
There we go. There we go.
Brilliant! Thank you so much.
- Thank you. Thanks.
- Thanks, boys. Thanks, fellas.
No worries!
Guys, we're here!
It's gonna be fun!
Just a quick recap now...
Look, look, look. There he is.
Don't you think he looks like
a sure thing, huh?
Will?
You're going to lose.
How would you know that?
His ears are flat, his coat is dull,
and he's got a funny walk.
Great.
So, you know everything
about horse racing, too.
No.
I just look, process information
and make decisions.
And that horse is
definitely not gonna win.
Yeah, well, I like him.
Sometimes you just have to
go with your gut.
I'm gonna go and place my bet.
They're lining up
at the gate now.
Good to see My Blue Heaven
back after injury.
State of Grace always
a bit reluctant going in.
They're under starter's orders.
And they're off!
Greek God setting a good pace
on the inside with Little Jim ju... Oh!
We seem to have a non-starter.
Man-Oh-Man apparently having a day off.
No, Aiden O'Connor looks like
he's just not going to get him going.
Well, the rest of the field
are now making their way
along the straight at a cracking pace.
This is nice.
Yeah, I love being spoon-fed in public.
Hello! We'd like
a table for three, please.
Of course. If I could just see your badge.
Sorry?
This restaurant's for
Premier Badge holders.
Oh, well, we've got the pink badges!
I'm sorry, we can only serve
Premier Badge holders.
Um, okay, are there any other restaurants?
Well, there's our relaxed dining area,
and there are stalls outside.
The Pig in a Poke does
a nice hog roast in a bun
with apple sauce.
Sharon. Can I call you Sharon? Yeah?
So it's a quiet Monday afternoon
and you've got a lot of empty tables.
We want to buy a really expensive meal.
We don't want to
eat pork rolls at a stall,
even with apple sauce.
Oh, I'm really sorry.
You need a Premier Area Badge.
It's policy.
Okay, okay, okay. So how much
for a Premier Area Badge?
What are we talking, like,
another 10? Another 20?
We don't sell badges, madam.
This is a restaurant.
You'll have to go to the ticket office.
Louisa. Let's go.
No, no, no. This is nuts.
We've come all this way.
Louisa.
I'm not hungry.
I'm just gonna run
and get the badges,
and then we will have our meal.
We'll be fine once we've eaten. Yeah.
Lou.
I think Will wants to go home.
You know what, Sharon?
You can stick your Premier Badge
right up your relaxed dining area.
Okay. Okay.
Everything's fine.
Great. So we're going to
paralyze your eardrums
as well, now, are we?
So, maybe horse racing
wasn't my best idea.
But this, I think you'll enjoy.
So Nathan's never been to
a classical music concert now?
No. I haven't.
Will you please come with me?
I bought the tickets a week ago.
You can say "no."
A wind concerto?
I've been assured
it doesn't involve farting.
There's no chance of Jay-Z?
Sadly, his tickets had just sold out.
Mozart it is, then.
Okay. Would this
be the right sort of thing
to wear to a concert?
Metallica, no.
Neil Diamond, possibly.
I thought Pat was training tonight.
Oh, no. He is.
He is. I'm taking Will to a concert thing.
Sorry, you're going on a date?
It's too booby.
Way too booby.
Given it's a man for whom your
boobs are mostly at eye-level.
Oh, you're so annoying!
You are so going on a date
with Will Traynor.
Get the red dress out.
Really?
Kapow!
Lose the scarf.
The scarf? Why?
If you're going to wear
a dress like that, Clark,
you have to wear it with confidence.
Only you, Will Traynor,
would tell a woman
how to wear a bloody dress.
- Here?
- Mmm-hmm.
- Am I good?
- Yeah! Yeah.
Yep, yep, Yep-Yep-
- Okay.
Is everything okay?
Mmm-hmm.
Actually, no, there's something
digging into my collar.
Okay.
It's a tag.
Have we got any scissors in the bag?
I don't know, Clark.
Believe it or not,
I rarely pack it myself.
Um... Okay, hang on.
Got it!
We should just be grateful
it wasn't in your trousers.
Oh, look. They're starting.
So you're not a classical
music person, then?
Hated every minute.
Yeah, I could tell.
Especially during that oboe solo.
There was something in my eye.
I loved it.
Did you?
Yeah.
Right, we'd better get you in.
Wait a minute, Clark.
You Okay?
I don't...
I don't want to go in yet.
I just want to be a man
who has been to a concert
with a girl in a red dress.
Just a few minutes more.
So, um...
Patrick wants to meet you.
Running man? Why?
I think he wants to know who I'm spending
all these late nights with.
My parents do, too.
I get nervous when a girl
asks me to meet her parents.
They wanted me to invite you to
my birthday dinner next Thursday.
But don't worry, I said
you wouldn't want to go.
Why'?
Because you hate strangers
and you don't like eating
in front of people.
Seemed pretty obvious.
I'll come.
If you want me to.
Ah! Lads, welcome.
Bernard Clark.
Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't...
A curtsy will be fine.
Curtsy. Nice one.
- This is Josie. My wife.
- Hello.
- Come on in.
- Yeah! Come in, come in.
Thank you.
Listen, have fun.
Thank you!
Dear Lord,
thank you for the food we eat,
and the company we keep.
Thank you for the
opportunities you give us,
and the strength to face the challenges
we meet on our journey.
Amen.
So, Will.
You bought and sold companies?
Something like that.
Would you know this fella,
Alan Stonehouse?
The one who...
What is it?
Asset stripped our firm?
I'm afraid I trained him.
Hmm.
Oh, well...
That's the door.
Some chicken, love?
Six miles in 28 minutes.
And a happy birthday to my girlfriend!
Yes! Happy birthday!
- Sorry I'm a bit late.
- Oh, no!
Only 28 minutes.
So couldn't you go back to it, Will?
I mean, clearly you're
still sharp as a tack.
- Dad!
- No. It's fine.
Truth is,
I thought I could crack this
and then go back,
as if nothing had changed.
Uh, I was wrong.
This is delicious, Mrs. Clark.
Oh! Josie, please!
Well, we wanted to make today special.
Wish Treena could have been here.
She's the brains of the family.
She got put up two years at school,
didn't she, Bernard?
Overtook our Lou.
Not bright enough to stop herself
getting up the duff though.
Pat, shall I help you
to some more chicken?
So, Patrick, Louisa tells me
you're a personal trainer.
Um, life coaching,
physical training, motivation.
Local young entrepreneur of the year,
two years running.
Lou tells me you were
a bit of an action man before.
Pat.
I bet if we got you on
a really good fitness regime.
There's actually a Swedish study about
how you can train muscles to remember...
Patrick!
What? I'm just trying to...
Yeah, well, don't.
I'll bear it in mind.
Thank you.
Um, so, I just wanted to say
we're very proud of you, love.
And, um... I don't know what we would
have done without you this past year.
Aw, Dad.
And, Will, thank you for employing her.
- Someone had to.
- Hey!
Pleasure's all mine.
Really.
- Oh!
- Here.
It's not much, but...
Granddad saw something on TV
about making your own presents.
Aw!
Granddad, thank you.
Thank you.
I love it. Mum, thank you.
Mine next.
Oh!
Go on, open it.
- I had it made specially.
- Oh...
Thank you, Patrick.
Oh!
Oh, WOW.
There's something for you
in my bag as well.
You got Lou a present?
That's very kind of you.
Wasn't that kind, Bernard?
That's very kind.
Okay.
On!
It's very lovely.
Oh, my God! I don't believe it!
- What?
- But where did you get them?
It's a secret.
Tights?
Only the best pair of tights, ever!
Oh, I'm gonna go try them on.
I'm gonna go try them on!
Oh, um...
I can't tell you how much I love them.
Really! Thank you.
I put some cake in your bag.
Thank you, Josie.
It's good to meet you all.
And, Patrick, thank you for the
fitness advice.
Just helping my girlfriend
get the best out of her job.
Oh, you're a lucky man.
She certainly gives a good bed bath.
Funny guy. I like him.
So, I could take you
to a Shakespeare festival.
It's happening today and tomorrow.
Or there's a sculpture park
we could visit.
Or there's... Ooh, there's wine tasting.
This came.
Ah.
Can I take you somewhere?
First kiss I ever had
was on that rampart.
Probably didn't hurt
that you owned the castle.
Maybe I should have told her.
She dumped me a week later for a boy
who worked at the local shop.
You're never gonna fit through there.
Oh, wow. It's amazing!
Will? Will! No, please!
Will, stop!
Are you coming?
This is a very bad idea.
It's very dangerous.
It's very, very high UP-
- And windy.
- Hmm.
When I was a kid, this used to
be my favorite place
in the whole world.
Did you walk around up here
pretending you were a warrior prince?
Even nicked a sword
from one of the exhibits.
Weighed a ton.
I think this would still be
my favorite spot.
- That's because you haven't been anywhere.
- Oh...
So where's better than this, then?
Val d'lsére?
Paris.
Place Dauphine, right by the Pont Neuf.
Sitting outside a café
with a strong coffee
and a warm croissant
with unsalted butter and strawberry jam.
So, let's go! We could get on
the Eurostar right now.
- No.
- But you just said...
You don't get it, Clark.
I want to be in Paris as me.
The old me.
With pretty French girls
giving me the eye.
Could be something to look forward to.
If I shut my eyes now,
I know exactly how it feels
to be in that little square.
I remember every sensation.
I don't want those memories erased
by the struggle to fit behind a table,
the taxi drivers who refuse to take me,
and my wheelchair power pack
that won't charge in a French socket.
I'll tell you where we will go, though.
Where?
Alicia's wedding.
Really?
Will you come with me?
If you want me to.
Hello?
- Whoo! Jesus, Mum, hello!
- Too much?
Oh, sod it. I don't care.
We are celebrating, Lou.
- I've got a job!
- Oh!
Dad, that is fantastic!
You are looking at the new
Head of Maintenance at the castle.
- God, that's just...
- I know. I know.
Mr. Traynor rang me himself.
So I'm starting tomorrow
morning, month's trial.
Isn't it brilliant? It's good money, Lou.
- And he gets his own van.
- Oh!
See you.
Okay.
I thought you'd be pleased.
No, I am! I am pleased.
I just... I don't know. I feel weird.
Well, don't.
Your dad needed a job,
mine needed a head of maintenance.
Yeah, but it's just the timing.
It's just a bit...
It's good.
Your dad will be great.
And it means...
It means what?
It means... It means that one day
you can go off and spread your wings
without worrying about everyone else.
Put yourself first, for once.
Hello.
Michael Lawler.
I'm here to see Mr. Traynor.
Oh, no, no, no. You've got the wrong door.
- He lives...
- It's okay, Clark.
How was traffic, Michael?
Oh, you know. Once you're out of London...
We'll sit in the courtyard.
You can leave us. Thanks, Clark.
How have you been?
Oh, well, thank you.
I thought he seemed happier.
He was smiling, laughing.
Me, too.
Well, thank you for telling me.
- Louisa.
- Yeah?
You will look after him
at the wedding, won't you?
I still don't know
why we're doing this.
We're going to behave admirably.
Just so you know,
if you do the My Left Foot thing,
I will drive home and leave you stuck here
with all your ex-girlfriends.
Spoilsport.
Ah!
Will, hi.
It's, uh... It's so good to see you again.
The office isn't the same without you.
One minute you were there
running everything and everyone,
and the next, well,
it's, uh, just not the same.
It's kind of you to say so, Freddie.
Ah, Oh...
Louisa Clark, Freddie Foster.
Yes! Yes, I saw you at the church.
Life isn't all bad then, eh?
Will.l.Am.
Anyway, anyway, must mingle.
It's good to see you, Will.
And you, Miss Clark.
He's a nice guy.
He fancies you.
He needs glasses.
Don't do that.
You look beautiful.
Well, you don't look so shabby yourself.
Ladies and gentlemen.
I give you the bride and groom,
Mr. and Mrs. Rupert Collins!
Oh, God!
There ought to be a law
against Englishmen on dance floors.
Bride or groom?
Oh, neither.
You'?
Godmother to the bride.
Which makes me morally
responsible for her.
Not one of my finer acts.
Oh, you don't think much of her, then?
This is a bit depressing.
Mmm.
Still, one can't do these things sober.
Oh, no, wait,
there's alcohol in this stuff?
Absolutely, darling.
And I firmly encourage you
to get as drunk as possible.
I hear rumors
that the father of the bride
is going to inflict another speech on us.
Oh, no. I'm supposed to be
driving Will home.
Ah, yes. Young Will.
He was her chance, you know.
Only one of that lot
that was worth a damn.
Terrible shame.
Well, he's not dead.
No, I meant for her, not him.
No, Rupert's an arsehole.
You take care of him.
He's a good one.
Take it from one who knows.
Four marriages and counting.
Thank you so much for coming, Will.
It was a lovely day.
I wouldn't have missed it for the world.
You remember Louisa?
Oh, yes. Yes.
Anyway, you're a real star for being here.
And thank you for the, um...
- For the...
- Mirror.
Yes, the mirror.
Absolutely love that mirror.
Anyway, thank you.
You didn't buy her a mirror.
I know.
Okay, you.
And, what do you say?
You gonna give me a whirl?
What? How many of those did you drink?
Come on, let's give these tossers
something to talk about.
- All right.
- Whoo.
- He's ruining everything.
- And her.
Are they all appalled?
Yes.
Yeah.
Move closer. You smell fantastic.
You never would've let
those breasts so near to me
if I wasn't in a wheelchair.
Oh. yeah?
Well, you never would've been
looking at these breasts
if you hadn't been in a wheelchair.
What? Of course, I would.
No, you wouldn't.
You would've been too busy
looking at the leggy blondes.
The ones who can smell
an expense account at 40 paces.
And, anyway, I would've been
over there serving the drinks.
One of the invisibles.
Am I right?
Yes, but in my defense...
I was an arse.
Yep.
Do you know something, Clark?
You are pretty much the only thing
that makes me want to get up
in the morning.
Then let's go somewhere.
Anywhere in the world. Just you and me.
What do you say?
Say yes, Will.
Go on.
- Okay.
- Yeah?
All the way to the hotel.
This is going to go very wrong.
You know that?
No, this is going to be brilliant!
On...
I don't think you're driving
in a straight line!
Why didn't you return
any of my calls?
I was worried sick.
Are you all right?
I think I'm old enough to
spend a night in a hotel
without permission, Mother, okay?
Okay.
Right.
I'm guessing she didn't do your tubes.
She did manage to get the
porter to help me into bed.
This is not good, mate. You're sweating.
Look at me. How's your eyesight?
I'm pretty sure you're Nathan. Am I right?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure you've
been on the drink. Am I right?
I'll be fine.
Jesus, Will.
We had a nice time.
You what?
I'm not coming to
Xtreme whatever-it's-called.
To Norway.
They need me at work!
But you said you'd support me.
I am supporting you, Patrick!
I hate cycling, and you know I do.
But there's this trip
I've got to go on with Will.
Why can't they just get an agency nurse?
Because it's my job!
What is this, Lou?
Your job seems to take priority
over everything these days.
Patrick, this is important, okay?
Trust me.
But it's Norway!
It's meant to be our holiday!
I just can't.
Oh, Pat.
He's stable.
But pneumonia?
He only had a cough on Saturday morning.
His lungs are weak,
any bacteria hits him hard.
Can I go in?
Oh, Camilla's with him.
Best leave her to it.
It's his fourth bout in two years.
The last one nearly killed him.
Thank you.
How's he doing?
He's a little better, I think.
Would you like me to
take over for a while?
I would really like to change my clothes.
Sure.
Hey.
How are you feeling?
Been better.
Oh, I don't know.
You'll do anything
for attention, Will Traynor.
I don't think I can do witty today, Clark.
Hey, just dropping off
- some meds for when he gets back.
- Mmm-hmm.
You all right?
Yeah, yeah.
Just, um, canceling everything.
You know, don't you?
Yeah.
Oh, I've been with him two years.
His life is hard.
He hides his pain when he's with you.
But there have been times
when I've stayed over,
and I hear him screaming.
In his dreams, he's still
running or skiing,
doing things, you know.
And then he wakes up
and there's nothing I can say to him.
Now, I can't judge what he wants to do.
That's his choice.
But that was before me.
Yeah, and I know that he did pretty much
anything to make you happy.
Look, I want him to live, Lou.
But only if he wants to live.
I can't just let this happen.
I can't.
And we're running out of time.
So, if I could come up with another trip
that the doctors would agree to,
would you come with us?
Yeah.
Of course I would.
Hi.
This is unexpected.
I've bought your parents cinema tickets
and Granddad's in his room.
Asleep, I think.
You bribed my parents
and jailed my granddad.
Good.
I am an idiot.
But this job of yours
is just for a few more weeks.
Things will soon be back to normal.
I should be proud that you're
doing something worthwhile.
I don't want to argue with you, Lou.
- Less than 300 calories.
- Mmm.
What's this?
Oh, it's the trip I told you about.
I thought you meant Lourdes or something.
"Hot tub under the stars."
"Massages. Swim with dolphins."
Oh, look. "Five-star luxury,
24-hour room service."
This isn't work.
Do you really expect me to just sit here
while you swan off with
another man on a honeymoon?
His other caregiver's coming, too.
Oh, two guys. That's all right, then.
Patrick, this is really important.
Do you know how this feels?
It's like I'm running permanently
just a little behind
the rest of the field.
It's like, there's something
bad around the bend,
and everyone seems to
know what it is except me.
Patrick...
Seven years we've been together, Lou.
You've known him five months.
But he needs me.
And I don't?
I'm sorry.
Well, you got him here.
- Cheers, mate.
- Thank you, sir.
Bienvenue.
Let me show you to your rooms.
Hey, you.
How are you feeling?
Better.
So, what's the plan for today?
Um, well, we can stay here for a bit.
Because they rent DVDs at the front desk.
We didn't come all this way
to watch DVDs, Clark.
Stop, stop. Hey!
Oh!
Is there alcohol in that?
Rum, vodka and Cointreau, sir.
She'll have two, please.
- Yes, sir.
- Thank you.
Oh, I booked you in
for scuba diving tomorrow.
Even after I said I didn't want to. Will!
- Hey!
- Hi.
- Hey.
I'm gonna walk Karen back to her hotel.
I'm just not sure she should
walk back alone.
Very chivalrous of you.
Yeah, it's very civic-minded.
Oh, piss off, the both you.
Yeah, I've got everything
covered, don't worry.
We'll be fine.
All right. Yeah, we'll see you later.
- Bye!
- Have fun.
No, don't.
Leave them open.
I wanna see it.
Don't go back to your room tonight, Clark.
- Just do it.
- No, I can't! I can't.
It's gonna be too deep, so I can't.
You can. You can do anything.
Mmm-mmm.
Why didn't you make me do that earlier?
That was amazing!
I don't know, Clark!
Some people just won't be told!
I don't wanna go home.
This has...
This has been the best.
You're glad you came, right?
Yes.
You.
You are something else, Clark.
Well.
I have to tell you something.
I know.
I know about Switzerland.
I have known for months.
Listen, I know this is not
how you would have chosen it,
but I can make you happy.
- No.
- What?
No, Clark.
I get that this could be a good life.
But it's not my life.
It's not even close.
You never saw me before.
I loved my life.
I really loved it.
I can't be the kind of man
who just accepts this.
You're not giving it a chance.
You're not giving me a chance.
I have become a whole new person
these last six months because of you.
I know. And that's why
I can't have you tied to me.
I don't want you
to miss all the things that
someone else could give you.
And selfishly, I don't want
you to look at me one day
and feel even the tiniest bit
of regret or pity.
I would never think that!
You don't know that.
I can't watch you
wandering around the annex
in your crazy dresses.
Or see you naked and not...
Not be able to do...
Oh, God, Clark, if you had any idea
what I wanna do to you right now.
I can't live like this.
Please. Will, please.
Listen.
This,
tonight, being with you
is the most wonderful thing
you could have ever done for me.
But I need it to end here.
No more pain and exhaustion
and waking up every morning
already wishing it was over.
It's not going to get better than this.
The doctors know it and I know it.
When we get back,
I am going to Switzerland.
So I'm asking you
if you feel the things you say you feel,
come with me.
I thought that
I was changing your mind!
Nothing was ever going to change my mind.
I promised my parents six months,
and that's what I've given them.
No!
No.
Don't say another word.
You're so selfish.
I tore my heart out in front of you,
and here all you can say is no.
And now you want me to come and watch
the worst thing
you could possibly imagine.
Do you have any idea what you're asking?
I wish I had never taken this stupid job!
I wish I had never met you.
Louisa.
Louisa!
You all right?
Fine.
Oh, look at you.
- You look wonderful!
- You do.
Great photos of you on the beach.
Swimming, too?
Yeah, it was great.
How was the flight?
Well, we got here in one piece.
Are you hungry? 'Cause we can eat
at the restaurant in the Intercontinental.
- I could eat.
- Excellent.
Louisa, let me give you a hand with those.
Actually, I need to get home.
Come on. We want to know how you got on.
Let her go.
Louisa!
Wait. Louisa, please.
You don't need to pay me.
I'm sorry.
Well?
Sit down, Josie, love. Please.
Lou's upset enough.
And his parents know?
I mean, what kind of people are they?
Mrs. Traynor doesn't know
what else she can do.
It's his choice.
Some choices you don't get to make.
He's not in his right mind.
People that are vulnerable
should not be given a chance to...
It's complicated, Mum.
- It is not. It's simple.
- Mum.
No. You can't be a part of this.
It's no better than murder.
I tried, Dad.
I tried so hard,
but I failed.
Who says you failed?
I'm not sure anyone in the world
could ever persuade that man,
once he'd set his mind to something.
You can't change who people are.
Then what can you do?
You love them.
No one could have done more than you.
You have a heart as big as that castle,
and I love you for it.
Have you seen them? Mr. Traynor?
They left. This morning.
Dad, have I made a huge mistake?
Call them.
You still have time.
Don't worry. Mum will come round.
I'll talk to her.
You're doing the right thing, Lou.
You have to go.
You were useless until you met him.
Hello.
He's just through there.
Okay.
Here.
Oh, thank you. Thanks.
Oh!
Sorry, I didn't mean to...
The familiar sound of Louisa Clark
making an entrance.
We'll leave you be.
Thank you.
Don't tell me.
You're here to make my last cup of tea.
Actually, no.
I'm here to kidnap you.
I'm gonna steal you and
I'm gonna take you to...
Where?
- Rio.
- Mmm.
Or my mum and dad's.
I haven't quite decided yet.
Open the doors, Clark.
Come here.
Closer.
Look at me.
Please, look at me.
I can't.
Tough.
I need to see that face.
I need to see that face of yours.
Even if it is all pink and blotchy.
You really are the most
impossible man, Will Traynor.
And the world will definitely
be a better place without me.
No.
No, it won't.
Don't be sad, Clark.
Tell me something good.
Will you stay?
For as long as you want me to.
Can you call my parents in?
Clark.
A few weeks should have passed
by the time you read this.
If you followed the instructions,
you'll be in Paris
on one of those chairs that never sit
quite level on the pavement.
I hope it's still sunny.
Across the bridge to your right
you will see L'Artisan Parfumeur.
You should try the scent
called Papillons Extréme.
I always did think
it would smell great on you.
There are a few things
I wanted to say and couldn't,
because you would have got all emotional
and you wouldn't have let me finish.
So, here it is.
When you get back home,
Michael Lawler will give you
access to a bank account
that contains enough
to give you a new beginning.
Don't start panicking.
It's not enough for you to sit around
for the rest of your life,
but it should buy you your freedom.
At least from that little town
we both call home.
Live boldly, Clark.
Push yourself.
Don't settle.
Wear those stripy legs with pride.
Knowing you still have
possibilities is a luxury.
Knowing I might have given them to you
has eased something for me.
So, this is it.
You are scored on my heart, Clark.
You were from the first day you walked in
with your sweet smile
and your ridiculous clothes.
And your bad jokes
and your complete inability to ever hide
a single thing you felt.
Don't think of me too often.
I don't want you getting sad.
Just live well.
Just live.
I'll be walking beside you
every step of the way.
Love, Will.